I don't like admitting that I became a commodity.
I confuse being admired with being loved.
Is it the likes or is it marketing?
Don't ask me for consistency.
I don't believe in religion.
I'm tired. But once again I force myself to work.
Guilt. Capitalism.
Neoliberalism. Optimism.
They don't let me rest.
I should consider being more considerate.
But please for your consideration.
I need to belong. I can't stop.
When I get sad on the internet, I find understanding.
And not in a figurative sense, because I'm anti-simulation.
Anti-actress, anti-singer, anti-Hellenist.
I'm a dumb feminist.
I have nothing to lose.
Let the world burn, because I've already won.
To be or not to be, that is the question.
My body pays for what my name earns.
Like a sentence. It's therapy.
I sell intimacy. Songs with ego and insecurity.
It's not ambition, it's survival.
And to be honest, I have no idea what I'm doing.
I want to sit on the toilet looking at my phone until my legs go numb.
Get as fat as I want, with no human interaction.
Watch TV shows all day.
But I must keep going. The world demands that I keep going.
That's why I ask for your consideration.
"Femme fatale," says a headline.
So casually.
As if they knew me.
As if I'm black in springtime.
Welcome. The show must go on.
I dress sadness in red satin.
With tons of solitude.
Pantomime on stage.
Accommodating, as always.
Dreaming of some sobriety.
I carry the chaos of promises with my lips.
A poem.
Lethal revolution.
I have nothing to lose.
Let the world burn.
I just wanted them to love me, nothing more.
I do it again, I burn it all down.
I'm an expert in the art of sabotage.
So many years trying to figure out who I am.
Maybe I am.
That femme fatale.
I carry chaos as a promise with my lips.
A poem in lethal revolution.
I have nothing to lose.
Let the world burn.
I just wanted to be loved, nothing more.
And to explain to you, my heart.
I am anxiety attacks.
In my voice, I have a kingdom of storms in spring.
Please, a big round of applause.
For the femme fatale.
Ready.
Let's go.
Monserrat, we need to have a serious talk
about expectations and insecurity.
That you do everything wrong. Who cares?
We're going to die. They're going to forget us anyway.
And I think about Botox and experimental music.
About my mother and the loneliness of a world tour.
Maybe I'll be better off when I don't try to be either young or normal.
Hide my ghosts and finally learn to love myself.
I should learn to love myself.
I'm going to pick up my pieces.
I want to learn to love myself,
but I know myself too well.
Hello Monserrat.
Hello Miss Empathy, my queen, who gives all of herself.
The complexity in me is a romantic poem with senile dementia.
I think about how many things I take for my mental health.
And how many taxes I have to pay this month.
Maybe I'll be better when I don't try to be young or normal.
Bury my ghosts and finally learn to love myself.
I should learn to love myself.
I'm going to pick up my pieces.
I want to learn to love myself, but I know myself too well.
Thank you.
Your dreams, past.
You have to give them a chance.
Miracles are just one day at a time.
On this journey, I want to sit next to you.
If you let me, I can go with you.
My stubborn heart won't give up.
You aren't empty.
I feel you when you kiss me.
I exist in your potential.
Love, how I would love.
For you to see yourself the way I see you.
I still believe that my love can save us.
Sometimes I am so afraid.
You are not like him.
Don't give him your heart.
Sometimes I am so afraid.
You are not like him.
Miracles are just one day at a time.
The miracle is you.
Love of my life.
I will never forget this trip with our seven-month-old son.
Right now, I'm on the ferry to Venice crying tears of joy.
I just love you so much. I love our friendship and every part of you.
I love your hair, your sense of humor, your vampire teeth.
Your scent, especially when you haven't showered.
I love when you get excited and your eyes fill with tears.
I love your kindness, your belly button, your neck.
I love seeing you smile with that sweet smile
that you make when you shrug your shoulders.
You know what I love most in life is our son's sweet face or anything about him.
Right now, there are only a few minutes until I can finally touch you.
I love you so much in the water, in the deepest depths.
At the lighthouse at midnight.
I love you so much.
OK.
Sorry.
Thank you.
Audience:
I love you!
I love you.
OK. Did my lipstick stay on?
Yes. No. My lipstick smudged.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Let's go.
Oh. Two, three.
Today I woke up.
I lit a cigarette and poured myself coffee.
I took my son to school and on the way back home I cried.
When I got back, I went to change my clothes.
I looked at myself naked in the mirror and cried again.
Who is that woman who looks more and more like my mom?
I took my six pills, put on a face mask.
I found a new wrinkle, for a change.
When I brushed my teeth, I laughed intensely.
It's another day. One more day.
I don't want to be bipolar.
I just want a normal life.
Sometimes I fall back down.
I think I'm a bit addicted to stress.
At least I quit drinking.
Even though I get bored, I know it's better this way.
So I go back to the pills.
More coffee and more cigarette butts.
I've buried myself in work, for a change.
I brush my teeth again.
I don't laugh, I'm zoned out.
It's another day, one more day.
None of that bipolar shit.
I just want a normal life.
And no, no, I won't let it defeat me.
The drama queen is in the past.
The femme fatale.
I'm going to quit smoking.
I'm going to lose weight.
I'll be the best mom.
I'll fix everything, boom, boom, boom everyday, every night!
I've never been better.
I'm full of love.
I will overcome.
And have the most extremely normal life.
My snot is everywhere. It's OK.
Well, that's fine. We're all set.
Ready? We're all set.
Felix:
Thank everybody, thank you for coming.